当我们起初定义我们的表的时候
When we first defined our tables,
我们定义他们之间的关系和约束条件
we defined the relationship between
them in terms of constraints.
我将会讲解怎么样实现关系在我们的
I'm going to show how we implemented
that relationship into our
查询中使用join
query using a join.
join允许我们查询weather使用从
This join allows us to
query the weather table for
位置设置里定义的一些值
values from a specific location setting.
在Sunshine的例子中，用户设置这些在偏好中
In Sunshine's case,
the user sets this in preferences.
你将注意到有一个SQLite query builder类
You'll notice that there's a SQ
lite query builder class for
在weather provider的顶部
able at the top of weather provider.
正如你可能会想到的 这个类帮助构建查询和
As you might guess,
this class helps construct queries and
被用到作为查询方法的基础
is actually used as the basis for
你已经在SQLite 数据类中有用到
the query functions you've already
used in the SQLite database class.
我们在这个类的静态块初始化这个SQLite query builder
We initialize the SQLite query builder
in the static constructor of the class.
描述这两个表之间的连接
Describing the join between both tables.
setTables方法填写SQL 查询的一部分内容
Set.Tables fills out the content
in the from part of the SQL query.
注意 两个表都有一个_ID 字段
Note, since both tables
have a field with an _ID,
我们必须使用表名来清除我们
we must explicitly use the table
name in order to disambiguate
讨论的是那个ID的歧义在多表查询中
which ID we are talking
about in the join.
然后我们定义了selection
Then we define the selection.
selection使用问号标记或者占位符
The selection is defined using
the question mark or placement syntax.
selection参数会替代这些值
The selection parameters
will replace these values.
正如你看到的 我们的selection有2个参数
As you can see,
our selection has 2 parameters,
一个位置设置和一个日期
a location setting and a date.
然后我们有一个方法来通过位置获取天气
Then we have a function to get the
weather by location setting using this
使用相同的query builder
same query builder.
注意 我们从URI取参数
Note that we fetch
the parameters from the URI.
然后构建这个string数组和这个string数组从而
And build the string array and
build the string array so
使他们代入我们的查询
that they can be
substituted into our query.
我们以这个方式建立的两个查询
We do that for both of the queries
that we're creating this way.
最终，我们把方法加入到content provider的日常查询中
Finally, we added the functions into the
query routine of the content provider
为带有位置和日期的天气和带有位置的天气
for both weather with location and
date and weather with location.